Beto mentioned that we should provide bit maps at different resolutions.
In our app, the 48 dib icon on the Nexus S
looks to be about the same size as on the Nexus
4, and on the Nexus 5. However, in reality, this asset
that's being displayed is actually a lot bigger in terms of
pixels compared to this one. To confirm, we can check out
the app resource folders. In the drawable folders, we see that
our app has a 48 by 48 pixel launcher icon for
mdpi devices located in the drawable mdpi folder. To
make an equivalent icon for the higher density devices,
we need to make that icon progressively larger. To
know exactly how big to make these images and
what the dibbed pixel conversion should be, we use
an mdpi device as the baseline. This is where
one dib equals one pixel. Then on the HDPI
device one dib equals 1.5 pixels. And then it increases
from there, all the way to an xx HDPI
device, where one dib equals four pixels. For more info
on the conversions, see the link below. Following those
rules, these are the sizes of the launcher icon in
our drawable folders. The MDPI one is 48 pixels
by 48 pixels. The one for HDPI is 1.5 times
the size of this one. From an XHDPI device,
the icon is two times the size of the MDPI
one, and for an XXHDPI device, the icon is the three times the size of this one.